Archives Organization File Additional records 5956
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box 31, Folder (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: Study Findings Challenge Stereotypes of Women, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    Survey of Working Conditions. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Comment on the Status of Women at the University, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    By University record. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Occupation, Employment and Lifetime, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    By Larry Suter. Work Experience of Women. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: What the Other Half Thinks: The Implications of Female Perceptions for Work Demands, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    By Rita Braito; Edward Powers. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Facts and Fictions About the American Working Woman, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    By Joan E. Crowley; Teresa E. Levitin; Robert P. Quinn. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Facts on Women Workers of Minority Races, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Item 18: Bluecollar Women get Organized, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
    By Vivian Pospisil. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Bluecollar Women get Organized, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Item 20: Bluecollar Women Get Organized, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Item 21: Job Discrimination Handbook, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Item 22: The Economic Role of Women, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Item 23: Women Workers Today, Publication (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Box 31, Folder (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Counseling Girls Toward New Perspectives, Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Why Women Work, Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Rapport au Gouvernement de la Tunisie sur la Preparation Professionnelle des Juenes Filles ae des Femmes en Tunisie, Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
    Item is in French.
  - Item 4: Who are te Working Mothers?, Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: The Working-Wife Household: I and II, Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Progress and Prospects, Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Report on Progress in 1966 on the Status of Women, Publication (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Box 31, Folder (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Employing Married Women, Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
    By Viola Klein. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Problems of Working Women, Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Industrialism and Woman's Status, Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Help Wanted - Female, Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
    By Georgina Smith. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Women in the Federal Service, Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
    By Women's Bureau. 1939-1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Changing Woman Worker, Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Factors Determining the Labor-Force Participation of Married Women, Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
    By Thomas Mahoney. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Employment Problems of Working Women, Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Women in High-Level Positions, Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: Suggestion to Women and Girls on Training for Future Employment, Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: Working Wives, Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
    By Consumer Markets. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Women in the Labor Force, Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: An Empirical Investigation of the Labor Market Activity of Women, Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
    By Research Program. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Women View their Working World, Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
    By Glenn Ramsey. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Economic Rights of Women, Publication (Box 31, Folder 6)
    By F. Le Gros Clark. Item is in English.
- Box 31, Folder (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Married Women in Industry, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
    By E. M. Harris. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Working Wives, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Women! It's Your Fight Too!, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Women in the Federal Service 1954, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Conference on the Creation of Conditions which will Enable Woman to Fulfil her Role in Society as Mother, Worker and Citizen, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
    IVth Congress. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Shortage of Young Women Workers, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Bibliography on Employment Problems of Older Women, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Bibliography on Employment Problems of Older Women, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: Employment of Older Women, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Programs and Services of the Women's Bureau, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
    By Women's Bureau. How to use Them. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Unemployment During and After Pregnancy, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
    By Division of Employment. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Women's Attitudes to Repetitive Work, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
    By David Cox. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Spotlight on women in the United States, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Item 14: Working Wives: An Econometric Study, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
    By Richard Rosett. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Women as Workers A Satistical Guide, Publication (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Box 31, Folder (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The American Woman, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
    By Women's Bureau. A Selected Bibliography of Basic Sources. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Economic Responsibility of Women Workers as Shown by a Women's Bureau Study of Women War Workers and their Postwar Employment Plans, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Household Employment, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
    By Women's Bureau. A Digest of Current Information. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Women as Workers, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: The Role of Women's Legislation in Meeting Basic Problems of Working Conditions, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
    By Elizabeth S. Magee. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Progress of Women in the United States, 1949-1951, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Some Aspects of the Nightwork Problem with Special Reference to the Restaurant Industry, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: Women who Work at Night, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
    By Edward Corsi. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Report on Trends in Night Work for Women in New York State Factories, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: Employment of Women in an Emergency Period, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: Women's Role in the Manpower Program, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 12: While Mothers Work at Defense Jobs, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 13: Rosie the Riveter is Coming Back, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
    By Frances Whitelock. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Median Age of Women in the Labor Force, 1900-1950, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 15: Recommended Standards for Employment of Women, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 16: Womanpower in Mobilization, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
    By Roma K. McNickle. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Women's Stake in Unions, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 18: Standards for Employment of Women, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 19: Women in Higher-Level Positions, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 20: Labor-Force Participation and Employment Opportunities for Women, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
    By Nedra Bartlett. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Why Women Work, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 22: A Report on Part Time Employment of Women, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
    By Based on Edna Noble White's Studies. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Women in Labor Unions, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
    By Gladys Dickason. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Working Wives and Mothers, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
    By Stella Applebaum. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Working Women and Unemployment Insurance, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 26: Women's Chances for Advancement in Business and Industry, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 27: Why do Women Work?, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 28: How to Supervise Women Employees, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 29: A Job for Women, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
    By Health resources Advisory Committee. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Special Problems in the Supervision of Women, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
    By Elinore Morehouse Herrick. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Employment of Women in Defense Production, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Box 31, Folder (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Some Questions Raised by the Employment of Women in War Industries, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
    By Gertrude Inwood. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Employment of Women in War Industries, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
    By L. C. Wagner. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Womanpower, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Differentials in Pay for Women, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Women and the War Effort, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
    By Robert Goodwin. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Wages of Women Workers, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
    By Mary Anderson. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Safeguarding the Woman Employee, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: Recruiting Women Workers, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: Why we Like Women in our Shop, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
    By W.G. Guthrie. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Women as Manpower, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
    By Katherine Glover. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Women Work, Women Vote, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 12: Women in War Work, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
    By The Franklin Institute. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: You're Going to Employ Women, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 14: Should Married Women Work?, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 15: Jobs and the Woman, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
    By Ruth Leach. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Women and the Top Jobs, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
    By Ruth M. Leach. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Women in Unions, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 18: Wartime reminders to Women who Work, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 19: Status of Women in Unions in War Plants, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
    By Women'sBureau. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Women in Brazil Today, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 21: Women at Work in Wartime, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 22: Women in War Industries, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 23: 50 Facts About British Women at War, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 24: Absenteeism and What Every Woman Should and Can do About it, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
    By Whitney Williams. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Working Conference on Women in Business and Industry, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 26: Women in Postwar Industry, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
    By Frederick Crawford. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: What Job is Mine on the Victory Line?, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 28: Analysis of State Equal Pay Laws as of October 15, 1945, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 29: Report on Conference on Women in War Industries, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
    By Women's Buresu. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Women in Personnel and Industrial Relations Work in War Industries, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 31: Journal of Social Case Work, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 32: Women's Wages in Wartime, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 33: Recommended Standards for Clothing and Personal Protective Equipment for Women Shipyard Workers, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 34: Women in Shipbuilding, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Box 31, Folder (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Supervising the Woman War Worker, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Women in War Work, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: War Jobs for Women, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Why Women Work, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Planning for Part-time Work, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Health and Welfare of Women in War Factories, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
    By Committee Report. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Women Who Work in New York, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: Safety Fashions for Women in Industry, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: American Women at War, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: Occupations Suitable for Women, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 11: Are You Equal to two German Women?, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 12: Information Notes on Women in War Industries, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 13: Women in War Industries, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
    By Department of Economics and Social Institutions. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Women in Defense Industries, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 15: Standards for Maternity Care and Employment of Mothers in Industry, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 16: War-time Employment of Women in the Iron and Steel Industry, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 17: Women's War Work in Britain, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 18: Employment of Women in War Production, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 19: Application of State Hour Laws to the Employment of Women on Defense Projects, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 20: Recreation and Housing for Women War Workers, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 21: Safety and Health Problems of Women in Industry, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 22: Use of Women as Makers of War Instruments Studied by Women's Bureau, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 23: State Hour Laws for Women Possible Excemptions in Periods of Emergency in Manufacturing Industries, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 24: Opinion of the Court, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 25: Women Workers in War Industries, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 26: Women in Defense Industries, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
    The Effect of the Increasing Employment of Women on Company Personnel Policies. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Plan Now for Women Workers, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 28: White House Announcement, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Box 32, Folder (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Women in Nontraditional Jobs: A Program Model, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Women in Nontraditional Jobs: A Conference Guide, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Young Women and Employment: What we Know and Need to Know About the School-to-Work Translation, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Employment and Economic Issues of Low Income Women: Report of a Project, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Women at Work, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By Henry Myers. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Women in Blue-Collar Jobs, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Women in the Economy: Full Freedom of Choice, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Minority Women Workers: A Statistical Overview, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: The Modern Woman in the Modern Union, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By Gloria Johnson. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Working Women for Freedom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By Angela Terrano; Marie Dignan; Mary Holmes. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: State Labor Laws in Transition: From Protetion to Equal Status for Women, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Employment Needs of Women Offenders: A Program Design, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Career Counseling for Women in the Federal Government, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By Federal Women's Program. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Working with Women: A Handbook for Men, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By Staff Recommendations. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Minority Women Workers: A Statistical Overview, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By Wmployment Standards Administration. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Mature Women Workers: A Profile, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Box 32, Folder (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Working Women and their Organizations, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    By Joyce Maupin. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Ten Women who Led the Struggle, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Box 32, Folder (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Women and the Economy, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
    By Andrew Kohen; Susan Breinich; Patricia Shields. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Commission on the Status of Women A Progress Report, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Organize! A Working Women's Handbook, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Box 32, Folder (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Seventh Annual Report of the Director of the Women's Bureau, Publication (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Short Hours Pay, Publication (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: A Study of Employability of Women in Selected Sections of the United States, Publication (Box 32, Folder 4)
    By Iva Lowther Peters. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Should There be Labor Laws for Women?, Publication (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: The Distinct Problem of Women Employees, Publication (Box 32, Folder 4)
    By Alfred Trembly. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Women in the Federal Service, Publication (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: The Married Woman and her Job, Publication (Box 32, Folder 4)
    By Edith Valet Cook. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Education for Marriage Series, Publication (Box 32, Folder 4)
    By Janet Fowler Nelson. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Women Workers of Michigan, Publication (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Women in Industry, Publication (Box 32, Folder 4)
    By Secretary of State. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Work Organization, Publication (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Box 32, Folder (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Toward Job Equality for Women, Publication (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Women, Publication (Box 32, Folder 5)
    By The conference Board. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Women Around the World, Publication (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Working-Class Women in a Changing World, Publication (Box 32, Folder 5)
    By Roger Coup; Shirley Greene; Burleigh Gardner. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Women in the Labor Movement, Publication (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: A Guide to Sources of Data on Women and Women Workers for the United States and for Regions, States, and Local Areas, Publication (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: From Sewing Machines to Politics: The Woman Union Member in the Community, Publication (Box 32, Folder 5)
    By Edna Raphael. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Changing Patterns of Women's Lives, Publication (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Sexual Harassment on the Workplace, Publication (Box 32, Folder 5)
    By Patricia Stover; Yvonne Gillies. Item is in English.
- Box 32, Folder (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Women at Work: A Century of Industrial Change, Publication (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Recent Legislative and Executive Action Restricting the Right of Marriage Women to Work, Publication (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Women's Industrial Conference Number, Publication (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Women's Hours and Wages in the District of Columbia in 1937, Publication (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Women in Business, Publication (Box 32, Folder 6)
    By Marketing Research Division. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Regional Conference of State Minimum-Wage Inspectors, Publication (Box 32, Folder 6)
    By Summary of Conference Discussions. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Experience as to Standards for Women's Work in Periods of Rapid Increases in Production, Publication (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Effect of So-Called Married Women Bill on Business in General, Publication (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: The Employer's Viewpoint on Regulatory Legislation for the Woman at Work, Publication (Box 32, Folder 6)
    By Charles Craigmile. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Protection for Working Women, Publication (Box 32, Folder 6)
    By Alice Hamilton. Item is in English.
- Box 32, Folder (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Conference on the Defence of Life, Publication (Box 32, Folder 7)
    By 4th Congress. Item is in English.
- Box 32, Folder (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Workmen's Compensation 1910-1952: Are Present Benefits Adequate?, Publication (Box 32, Folder 8)
    By Harold Katz; Estelle Wirpel. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Development of Workmen's Compensation Claims Administration in the United States and Canada, Publication (Box 32, Folder 8)
    By Marshall Dawson. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Current Issues in Workmen's Compensation, Publication (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Forces that Spiral Workmen's Compensation Costs, Publication (Box 32, Folder 8)
    By Joseph Keiper. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: What's Wrong With Workmen's Compensation, Publication (Box 32, Folder 8)
    By John P. Owen. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Rising Cost of Workmen's Compensation Cases and New Methods of Control, Publication (Box 32, Folder 8)
    By Stanwood Hanson. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Workmen's Compensation, Fifty Years in Review, Publication (Box 32, Folder 8)
    By William Schnitzler. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Some Monetary Aspects of Wokmen's Compensation, Publication (Box 32, Folder 8)
    By Council on Industrial Health. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Web and the Rock in Workmen's Compensation, Publication (Box 32, Folder 8)
    By James Reid. Item is in English.
- Box 32, Folder (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Workmen's Compensation, Publication (Box 32, Folder 9)
    Selected References 1969-1971. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Workmen's Compensation: A Bibliography, Publication (Box 32, Folder 9)
    By Margaret Chaplan. Item is in English.
- Box 32, Folder (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Manpower Utilization in the Railroad Industry, Publication (Box 32, Folder 10)
    By Morris Horowitz. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Featherbedding, Work Rules, Restriction of Output, Publication (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Trends in Discipline and Work Rules, Publication (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: A Ray of Light in the Work Rules Dispute, Publication (Box 32, Folder 10)
    By H. E. Gilbert. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Labor and Industrial Relations Center, Publication (Box 32, Folder 10)
    By Charles Killingsworth. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Work Rules and Practices in Mass Production Industries, Publication (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: The Work-Rules Dispute, Publication (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: Union Work Rules: A Brief Theoretical Analysis and Some Empirical Results, Publication (Box 32, Folder 10)
    By Paul Hartman. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Work Rules Issue in the Railroad Labor Dispute, Publication (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Box 32, Folder (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Guidelines for the Desigh of New Careers, Publication (Box 32, Folder 11)
    By Sidney Fine. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Informal Factors in Career Achievement, Publication (Box 32, Folder 11)
    By Melville Dalton. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Increasing Job Satisfaction of White-Collar Workers, Publication (Box 32, Folder 11)
    By Karlton Pierce; Thomas Beaver. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: A Study of Job Adjustment, Publication (Box 32, Folder 11)
    By Robert Carlson; Rene Dawis. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Promoting the Will to Work, Publication (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Box 32, Folder (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Job Satisfaction - A Review of Literature, Publication (Box 32, Folder 12)